Guide to the Papers of Richard Phillips Feynman, 1933-1988
Archives
- Group II
  - Section III: Space Shuttle "Challenger" Investigation
    - Reports
      - NASA, "Actions to Implement the Recommendations of the Presidential Commission..." 14 July 1986 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Reagan, Ronald 19 June 1986 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Notes for "Mr. Feynman Goes to Washington" (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Newsclips (Box 38, Folder Folders 9-10)
  - Section IV: Course And Lecture Notes
    - Part A: Caltech Course Notes and Related Material
      - Bi/CS/Ph 250: Physics of Computation 1981-83 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - CS/Ph 187a Potentialities and Limits of Computing Machines 1984 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Computer Course 1981-84 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Computer Energetics 1980 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Fundamentals Course (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Gell-Mann Course Notes, Physics 234 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Gravity Course Notes ca. 1967 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Mathematical Methods of Physics II (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous Course Notes "Fresh" (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous Course Notes Quantum Mechanics and QED (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Notes for Talk to Gell-Mann's Class (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Physics 2a: Miscellaneous Notes (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Physics 2b: Miscellaneous Notes 1962 [?] (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Physics 2c: Miscellaneous Notes 1962 [?] (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Physics 125: Elementary Quantum Mechanics 1974 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Physics 135: Applications of Quantum Mech. 1979 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Physics 205: Advanced Quantum Mechanics 1973 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Physics 205a: Advanced Quantum Mechanics 1966-67 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Physics 205a 41.1 n.d.; 41.2 1978 (Box 41, Folder Folders 1-2)
      - Physics 205b: Notes and Calculations 1974-5 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Physics 205c: Relativistic Quantum M., Notes 1968 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Physics 230: High Energy Physics 1968-9 (folder 5) vol I; (folder 6) vol II (Box 41, Folder Folders 5-6)
      - Physics 230: Elementary Particle Theory 1987-88 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Physics 230b: Elementary Particle Theory Notes 1/19/[?] (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Physics 231: Experimental High Energy Physics 1970 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Physics 231: High Energy Physics 1975 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Physics 234: Field Theory 1978 (folder 4) vol I; (folder 5) vol II (Box 42, Folder Folders 4-5)
      - Physics 234: Photon-Hadron Lecture Notes 1971 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Physics 234: Photon-Hadron 1971-72 vol I (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Physics 234: Photon-Hadron 1971-72, (folder 1) vol II; (folder 2) vol III; (folder 3) vol IV (Box 43, Folder Folders 1-3)
      - Physics 234: QCD (folder 4) 1982; (folder 5) Course Notes n.d.; (folder 6) Course Notes 198[?]; (folder 7) Lecture Notes 1983 (Box 43, Folder Folders 4-7)
      - Physics 236: Gravity 1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Soph[omore] Lecture 13 April 1973 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Part B: Student Exams, Papers, Etc.
      - CS/Ph 187a: Student Problem Sets 1984 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - CS/Ph 251: Final papers 1984 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Homework and Exams--Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Physics 205: Homework 1974 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Physics 236b: Relativity Exams 1981 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Physics Candidacy Exam & Results 1971; 1976 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Student Papers/ Grades 1973-84 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Part C: Other Lecture Notes
      - Hughes Aircraft Courses given by Feynman
        - Lectures on Astronomy, notes by J. Neer 1966-67 (folder 1) Part I; (folder 2) Part II (Box 45, Folder Folders 1-2)
        - Lectures on Electrodynamics and Related Topics, notes by J. Neer Oct 1967-Jun 1968, (folder 3) Part I; (folder 4) Part II (Box 45, Folder Folders 3-4)
        - Lectures on Quantum Mechanics, notes by J. Neer July 1968-May 1969 (folder 5) Part I; (folder 6) Part II (Box 45, Folder Folders 5-6)
        - Lectures on QED, notes by J. Neer 196[9]? (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Feynman's Notes on Hughes Courses
        - "Hughes Computer" 7 Mar-17 Oct 1984 (Box 46, Folder 1)
        - "Hughes Computers 1983-4" Notebook (Box 46, Folder 2)
        - "Hughes--Electromag" Notebook Oct 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
        - "Hughes Notes, Electrostatics and Computers"14 Nov 1984 to 9 Jan 1985 (Box 46, Folder 4)
        - "Hughes Notes" (Box 46, Folder 5)
        - "Hughes Optics 1971-72" Notebook and Enclosed Material (Box 46, Folder 6)
        - "Miscellaneous" Lecture Notes (Box 46, Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 46, Folder 8)
        - "Old Hughes" notes (Box 46, Folder 9)
        - "Quantum Electronics--Hughes, Culver City 1977," Notebook and Enclosed Material (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Feynman's Notes Used for Other Lectures
        - "Lecture Ideas" (Box 46, Folder 11)
        - Lectures on Gravitation #1-11 1962-63 (Box 46, Folder 12)
        - Lectures on Gravitation #1-11; #12-16 in rough form ca 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1)
        - Lectures on the Theory of Fundamental Processes 1959-60 (Box 47, Folder 2)
        - Les Houches Course on Gauge Theories 2 1976 (Box 47, Folder 3)
        - Les Houches Summer School Lectures 1976 (Box 47, Folder 4)
        - Mautner Lectures on QED, Notes 1983 (Box 47, Folder 5)
        - Statistical Mechanics Course Notes (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - Statistical Mechanics Problem Sets (Box 47, Folder 7)
        - Statistical Mechanics: A Set of Lectures 1960-61 (Box 47, Folder 8)
        - Statistical Mechanics: A Set of Lectures 1960 (folder 1) Part I; (folder 2) Part II; (folder 3) Part III; (folder 4) Part IV (Box 48, Folder Folders 1-4)
  - Section V: Talks, Speeches, Conferences
    - Part A: Dated talks
      - The Value of Science NAS Meeting, Caltech, 1955 Nov 2-4 (Box 49, Folder 1)
        - Holograph notes, 1,1-4 leaves; proof, 1 p
      - Conflict of Science and Religion [ca 1956] (Box 49, Folder 2)
        - Holograph notes, [5] leaves; proofs, 2 pp
      - Theoretical Ideas Used in Analyzing Strange Particles Feynman and Gell-Mann, United Nations Talk [1960s] (Box 49, Folder 3)
        - Typescript (carbon)
      - Seeking New Laws (Messenger Lecture #3) Cornell, 1964 Nov (Box 49, Folder 4)
        - Holograph notes, [3] leaves
      - My Experiences with Quantum Electrodynamics Caltech Physics Colloquium, 1965 Dec 2 (Box 49, Folder 5)
        - Typescript, 33 leaves (incomplete, pp. 10, 14, 17 missing)
      - [Talk, CERN] 1965 Dec 17 (Box 49, Folder 6)
        - Typescript; audio tape
      - What is Science? National Science Teachers Association, New York, 1966 April 2 (Box 49, Folder Folders 7-10)
        - (folder 7) Correspondence, general 1965-67; (folder 8) correspondence, The Physics Teacher 1967-69; (folder 9) typescript (photocopy), with holograph corrections, 32 leaves; (folder 10) Ed Hutchings's typescript (photocopy), 32 leaves
      - The Principles of Relativistic Quantum Mechanics American Physical Society, Washington, 1966 April (Box 49, Folder Folders 11-12)
        - (folder 11) Correspondence, general 1965-67; (folder 12) notes (photocopy) by J. Ashkin; correspondence 1966-67
      - The Application of Mathematics to Mathematics Mathematical Society of America, Eugene, 1969 Aug (Box 49, Folder 13)
        - Holograph notes, [2] leaves; abstract, correspondence
      - The Behavior of Hadron Collisions at Extreme Energies Third International Conference of High Energy Collisions, Stony Brook, 1969 Sept 5-6 (Box 49, Folder Folders 14-15)
        - (folder 14) Holograph, 1-10, 10a, 11-19 leaves; typescripts (one photocopy); (folder 15) publication correspondence 1969-70
      - [Lecture, Oersted Medal] American Association of Physics Teachers, 1972 Feb 1 (Box 49, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence 1971-72, 1980-81; typescript (photocopy), ill.
      - What Neutrinos Can Tell Us About Partons Neutrino Conference, Balatonfüred (Hungary), 1972 June 11-17 (Box 49, Folder Folders 17-18)
        - (folder 17) Correspondence 1972; (folder 18) holograph, [i], 1-2, 2a, 3-7, 7a-c, 8-21, [3] ill. leaves; typescripts (one photocopy)
      - Final State Hadrons from Deep Inelastic Collisions XVI International Conference on High Energy Physics, Batavia, 1972 Sept 6-13 (Box 49, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence 1972; typescript
      - [Talk, particles] Caltech, Ramo Auditorium, [1973] (Box 49, Folder 20)
        - Typescript
      - [Talk on quarks] 1973 Jan 11 (Box 50, Folder 1)
        - Holograph notes, III leaves
      - The Internal Structure of the Proton Museum of Science and Industry, 1973 May 3, and Lawrence Berkeley Laboratory, 1973 May 10 (Box 50, Folder 2)
        - Holograph notes, [1] leaf
      - Partons Fifth Hawaii Topical Conference in Elementary Particle Physics, Honolulu, 1973 Aug 7-20 (Box 50, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence and documents 1972-74
      - The Structure of the Proton (Niels Bohr Medal Lecture) Copenhagen, 1973 Oct 3 (Box 50, Folder Folders 4-5)
        - (folder 4) Correspondence 1973-76; (folder 5) typescript, slides, figures, transparency
      - Conference on Lepton Induced Interactions UC Irvine, 1973 Dec 7-8 (Box 50, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence 1973
      - Summary Talk Fourth International Conference on Neutrino Physics, Philadelphia, 1974 April 26-28 (Box 50, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence 1973-74; typescript (photocopy); holograph notes (part photocopy), 1-2, [6] leaves; transparencies
      - Cargo Cult Science Caltech Commencement Address, 1974 June 14 (Box 50, Folder 8)
        - Holograph notes, [1] leaf; correspondence and documents, 1974
      - The Structure of the Proton Canadian Undergraduate Physics Association, 1974 October (Box 50, Folder 9)
        - Holograph notes, [3] leaves; slide masters
      - The Structure of the Proton and other talks Canadian Undergraduate Physics Association (Box 50, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence 1974-75, 1977-78
      - Remarks on New Particle 1974 Nov 13-26 (Box 50, Folder 11)
        - Typescript
      - Los Alamos from Below UC Santa Barbara, 1975 Feb 6 (Box 50, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence 1975-81; typescript (photocopy)
      - Talk to Math Club 1975 April 22 (Box 50, Folder 13)
        - Holograph notes, [4] leaves
      - [From folder:] Ψ talk 1975 Oct 14 (Box 50, Folder 14)
        - Holograph notes, 6 leaves; transparencies
      - [From folder:] Ψ talk Stanford Conference [1975?] (Box 50, Folder 15)
        - Transparencies
      - Summary Talk Conference on Quarks and New Particles, Laguna Beach (UC Irvine), 1975 Dec 5- 6 (Box 50, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence 1975
      - [Talk, Sigma Pi Sigma], CSU Long Beach, 1976 Jan 31 (Box 50, Folder 17)
        - Correspondence 1975-76
      - Negative Probability [1977] (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence; typescript, ill.; transparencies
      - Correlations in Hadron Collisions at High Transverse Momentum, Orbis Scientiae, Coral Gables, 1977 Jan (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence 1976-77; typescript, ill.
      - [Talk on Jesse DuMond] 1977 Feb 24 (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - Holograph notes, 4 leaves [small] and 4 leaves; transparencies and ill.; slides; typescripts (one photocopy)
      - Quark Jets VIII International Symposium on Multiparticle Dynamics, Kaysersberg (France), 1977 June 12-17 (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence 1976-77; typescript, ill.
      - [Talk at Lawrence Berkeley Laboratory] 1978 March 27 (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence 1978
      - [Talk on neutrinos], Caltech Alumni Seminar Day, 1978 May 13; and JPL and other related notes (Box 51, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence 1978; holograph notes, [5] leaves; transparencies, slides, misc
      - Omni Magazine interview, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence 1979; typescripts (photocopy)
      - How Well Do We Really Know What QCD Says About Large Momentum Transfer Processes? Caltech Physics Workshop, 1979 Feb 13-18 (Box 51, Folder 8)
        - Holograph notes, [3] leaves; documents
      - Robb Lectures [QED] University of Aukland, 1979 July-Aug (Box 51, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence 1978-79
      - Beatty Lectures: Light and Matter [cf Robb Lectures] McGill University, 1979 Oct 29-31 (Box 51, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence 1979
      - [From envelope:] YMZ Early Talks (Box 51, Folder Folders 11-13)
        - (folder 11) Stanford, 1980 Oct 29; Caltech, 1980 Nov 4; (folder 12) Crete [1980?]; (folder 13) QCD old [1980?] Transparencies
      - Simulating Physics with Computers MIT Conference on Physics and Computing, 1981 May 6-8 (Box 51, Folder Folders 14-16)
        - (folder 14) Correspondence, typescripts, list of attendees, photo; (folder 15) holograph notes, [1], V leaves; transparencies; (folder 16) copies of papers by others
      - A Qualitative Discussion of Quantum Chromodynamics in 2 + 1 Dimensions International Conference on High Energy Physics, Lisbon, 1981 July 9-15 (Box 51, Folder 17)
        - Typescript (photocopy)
      - How QCD Works Shelter Island, [1983?] (Box 51, Folder 18)
        - Correspondence 1983; transparencies
      - Probability in Mathematics Mathematical Association of America, San Diego, 1983 March 4 (Box 51, Folder 19)
        - Holograph notes, [9] leaves
      - [From folder:] QCD Elementary, Alaska University of Fairbanks, 1983 March (Box 52, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence 1982-83; transparencies
      - Tiny Computers Obeying Quantum Mechanical Laws Los Alamos, 1983 April 14 (Box 52, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence 1982-83
      - Conference on Chemically-Based Computer Design UC Los Angeles, 1983 Oct (Box 52, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence 1983; conference report
      - [From folder:] QCD Caltech Oct 1983 (Box 52, Folder 4)
        - Holograph notes, [1] leaf; transparencies
      - [Talk on QCD] UC Irvine Undergraduate Physics Conference, 1984 April 7 (Box 52, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence 1984
      - Quantum Mechanical Computers CLEO/IQEC Meeting, Anaheim, 1984 June 19 (Box 52, Folder 6)
        - Typescript, ill.; proofs
      - U.S. New and World Report Interview 1985 Feb (Box 52, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence; typescript
      - Quantum Mechanical Computers General Research Colloquium, Bell Labs[?], 1985 May 24 (Box 52, Folder 8)
        - Holograph notes, [18] leaves (one blank); notes, misc, [5] leaves; transparencies, article by S. Wolfram
      - Computing Machines of the Future AAAS Youth Symposium, 1985 May 29 (Box 52, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, documents 1985
      - Computing Machines of the Future Nishina Memorial Lecture, Tokyo, 1985 Aug 9 (Box 52, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence 1983-85; typescript
      - Bethe Ansatz Lunch talk 1987 Jan 22 (Box 52, Folder 11)
        - Holograph notes, [8] leaves
    - Part B: Undated talks
      - The Future for Science (Box 52, Folder 12)
        - Interview transcript (photocopy)
      - Science in America (Box 52, Folder 13)
        - Holograph, 4 leaves
      - Esalen II (Box 52, Folder 14)
        - Holograph notes, [2] leaves
      - It's As Simple as One, Two Three (Box 52, Folder 15)
        - Typescript
      - Algebra Machine (Box 52, Folder 16)
        - Holograph notes, [2] leaves
      - [Talk on math] (Box 52, Folder 17)
        - Holograph notes, a-c leaves
      - [From folder:] Relativity and QM Talk (Box 52, Folder 18)
        - Holograph notes, [7] leaves loose, [8] leaves on tablet; transparencies
      - [Talk on gravitation] (Box 52, Folder 19)
        - Holograph notes, 3, [3] leaves
      - Renormalization of the Gravitational Field International Conference on the Theory of Weak and Strong Interactions, La Jolla (Box 52, Folder 20)
        - Holograph notes, [18] leaves; documents
      - Cosmic Radiation (Box 53, Folder 1)
        - Holograph notes, [6] leaves
      - [Talk on theories of fundamental particles] (Box 53, Folder 2)
        - Typescript
      - Independent particles approximation (Box 53, Folder 3)
        - Holograph notes, [4] leaves
      - In Hawaii [talk on particles] (Box 53, Folder 4)
        - Holograph notes, 4 leaves
      - [From envelope:] Transparencies for Quark Talk, Hawaii (Box 53, Folder 5)
        - Transparencies
      - [Talk on quarks] (Box 53, Folder 6)
        - Holograph notes, V, [1] leaves
      - [From envelope:] Vancouver Transparencies (Box 53, Folder 7)
        - Holograph notes, [2] leaves loose, [4] leaves on tablet; transparencies, envelope
      - [Talk on particles] (Box 53, Folder 8)
        - Transparencies
      - [Talk on particles] (Box 53, Folder 9)
        - Holograph notes, [2] leaves
      - Why There are Anti-Particles (Box 53, Folder 10)
        - Polaroid slides (8)
      - [Talk on Self Action] (Box 53, Folder 11)
        - Holograph notes, 3 leaves
      - Parity for Electrons (Box 53, Folder 12)
        - Holograph notes, [6] leaves
      - [Talk on QCD] Lisbon [?] (Box 53, Folder 13)
        - Holograph, 1-8, a-c, 9-10, [4] leaves; transparencies
      - MIT Colloquium QCD (Box 53, Folder 14)
        - Holograph notes, [1] leaf
      - QCD Caltech (Box 53, Folder 15)
        - Holograph notes, [1], 4 leaves; transparency
      - [Untitled talk, incomplete] (Box 53, Folder 16)
        - Holograph, pag. 14-40, 40[sic]-53, 50-62
      - Notes, misc, possibly talk-related (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, lectures and talks 1973-1987, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Printed material, conferences and talks (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - Talk-related slides and negatives:
        - 6 envelopes
      - Legends to slides
        - 1 folder
  - Section VI: Publications
    - Amplifier Response (Manhattan Project report) 1946 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Slow Electrons in a Polar Crystal 1954-1962 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, holograph notes, typescript (carbon)
    - A Theory of the Fermi Interaction 1957 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Preprint (mimeo)
    - The Present Status of Quantum Electrodynamics 1961 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Typescript (photocopy)
    - There's Plenty of Room at the Bottom 1962 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Technion Yearbook 1962
    - The Feynman Lectures ca 1962-64 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Holograph notes enclosed with annotated copies of Part 2C: [35] leaves, [1] small leaf; corrections to v. 3
    - The Feynman Lectures 1963 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Annotated copies of Part 2C (2 copies)
    - The Theory of a General Quantum System... 1963 Preprint (mimeo) (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - The Group U(6) x U(6) Generated by Current Components 1964 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Preprint (photocopy)
    - The Development of the Space-Time View of Quantum Electrodynamics (Nobel Lecture) 1966 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Preprints (bound)
    - What is Science? 1969 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Edited typescript, galley proofs
    - Very High Energy Collisions of Hadrons 1969 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, typescripts with corrections, reprint with holograph notes
    - The Behavior of Hadron Collisions at Extreme Energies 1969 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Preprint (photocopy)
    - The Delta-I=1/2 Rule from the Symmetric Quark Model 1970 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Holograph MS, corrected typescripts, preprint (photocopy), correspondence
    - Closed Loop and Tree Diagrams 1970 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, typescript and ill. (photocopy)
    - Some Comments on Baryonic States 1970 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, typescripts with corrections, preprint
    - The Velocity Acquired by an Electron in a Finite Electric Field in a Polar Crystal 1970 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Typescripts (photocopy)
    - Current Matrix Elements from a Relativistic Quark Model 1970 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Typescript, ill.; holograph notes, [3] leaves; preprint (photocopy) with annotations
    - Cerenkov Effects in Tachyon Theory 1970 or after (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Typescript (photocopy)
    - Problems in Quantizing the Gravitational Field... 1971 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Typescript
    - Statistical Mechanics 1972 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Annotated copy
    - Statistical Mechanics ca 1972-74 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Holograph notes enclosed with annotated copy: [18] leaves (some photocopy); [3] leaves, misc
    - Structure of the Proton 1973 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Typescript (photocopy)
    - [Typescript, untitled] 1975 Oct 24 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Correlation Among Particles and Jets Produced with Large Transverse Momenta 1977 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Preprint (photocopy)
    - Quark Elastic Scattering as a Source of High Transverse Momentum Mesons 1977 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Preprint (photocopy)
    - A Parameterization of the Properties of Quark Jets 1977 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Preprint (photocopy)
    - A Quantum Chromodynamic Approach for the Large Transverse Momentum... 1978 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Typescript (photocopy); holograph notes, [15] leaves; envelope, preprint (photocopy)
    - Frontiers in Science (anniversary ed.) 1979 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, reprints
    - Qualitative Behavior of Yang-Mills Theory in 2+1 Dimensions 1981 (Box 57, Folder Folders 6-9)
      - (folder 6) Typescripts, ill.; (folder 7) correspondence and documents; (folder 8) preprints (photocopies) with corrections; (folder 9) typescript corrections, proofs
    - Simulating Physics with Computers 1981 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Typescript (photocopy) with holograph annotations
    - A Qualitative Discussion of Quantum Chromodynamics in 2+1 Dimensions 1981 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Preprint (photocopy)
    - Quantum Mechanical Computers 1984 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence 1984-87; typescript (edited), printed matter
    - QED, Russian Edition (L. B. Okun) ca 1986 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, printed matter
  - Section VII: Working Notes And Calculations
    - 1966-67 Blue Binder (Box 58, Folder Folders 1-6)
    - 1968-69 Blue Binder (Box 58, Folder Folders 7-10)
    - 1969-70 Green Binder (Box 59, Folder Folders 1-3)
    - 1976-77 Blue Binder (Box 59, Folder Folders 4-7)
    - 1976-77 Black Binder (Box 60, Folder Folders 1-4)
    - 1976-79 Brown Binder (Box 60, Folder Folders 5-7)
    - 1980 Yellow Binder (Box 61, Folder Folders 1-4)
    - 1981-82 Orange Binder (Box 61, Folder Folders 5-7)
    - 1982-83 Red Binder (Box 61, Folder Folders 8-10)
    - 1987-88 Black Binder (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - A Conventional Derivation of the Path Integral Minimum Principle 9/77 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - A Description of a Field Theory in 4-Space (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - "A Model of Strong and Weak Couplings" 20 Oct 1958 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Advanced Effects (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Algebra Vol A (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Algebra Machine (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Alternate Way to Handle Electrodynamics 13 Dec 1963 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Artificial Intelligence 1985 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Astronomy ca 1960 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Astrophysics (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Atomic Computer ca 1982 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Beta [Β] decay (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Binding energies of Fermi Gases [?] (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Biological Notes, The Structure and Action of Proteins and enclosed notes (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - CPT, Spin, Elementary Relativistic Quantum Mechanics (folder 2) ca 1967; (folder 3) "to T. H. and return to E. S." 1968; (folder 4) "Why Anti-particles, TCP etc." ca 1968 (Box 63, Folder Folders 2-4)
    - Calculations [?] ca 1980 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Calculations, Path Integrals, QCD, Computers 198[?] (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Calculations, Probability of σ=ρ(σ)δσ [?] (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Calculations by Forward Electron Theory with Opposite Charge (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Calculations from (H+λ×υ)4=ΕΨ (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Calculations of Resonance Widths ca 1970 (Box 63, Folder 10)